That's right.
I'll be able to reconvene
with Malone in about an hour.
Gyacho, I'm leaving this
job to you and Malone.
I think it's better to have the both
of you on this job, just to be safe.
I'll work to piece together
the clues back on this end.
Got it, Risotto.
How much longer will
this take? Step on it.
You should be able to
reconstruct it, no problem.
Rizzolto, you do know there are consequences
for going against Passione, right?
You're lucky I'm short on time.
Your left eye will be next.
All you need to do your job is
your right arm and right eye.
You should know better
than anyone how it works!
The boss makes all traitors
disappear from the face of...
Let's go.
Fighting God
What?
The hand you just severed has already
changed itself into another organism,
one that's ready to devour you.
You guessed it, it's now a piranha.
That attack totally ripped this
bastard open from the inside out.
How is he still moving?
What's wrong?
Speak to me, baby head.
Say something. Come on.
Huh?
That dirty turtle shit
is all over my face.
I don't deserve this kind of
torture and humiliation, you hear?
Aw, dammit!
I swear I'm gonna be scarred for life!
I'll make you pay dearly for this!
You'll die like a pathetic mutt
in a shit pool of your own shame!
I'm not gonna say this again.
If I have to take you out in order
to heal Bucciarati and Trish,
then that's what I'll do.
It's over!
I'll aim for that ugly head of yours next!
Eat your heart out!
And perish, you dickhead!
Shit of all the remote
tracking is great until daddy's
little death machine
decides to go off the rails.
You've attacked me three times
now, and I see right through you!
It's range got even longer.
Baby's growing up quite fast.
His temper and growth
are connected together.
Oh, di molto!
The shrew turned out to be the
stand mother of the freaking year.
Let's keep it simple.
I'm snuffing out this big talking
prick, and I'll do it any way I please!
Reverse course now, golden
wind! Now dive! Let's dive!
Yutie!
Direct hit.
Try using your eyes.
Your fist didn't come
anywhere near my face.
I win, punk.
Now you die!
All this struggling, it's useless.
What the?
My hand!
What's the problem?
Don't tell me you really thought Golden
Wind was playing fetch with his own hand.
It was the bike.
I turned the bike into a hand and
had it delivered right here to you.
Seems you noticed, but you just
assimilated that machine into your body.
That's excellent work.
Those third-rate tricks,
they won't work on me.
I'll just split apart and go.
You're forgetting.
Bikes need tanks of gasoline to run.
It'd be a simple task to
light you up before the
thought of running away
even crossed your mind.
On fire.
It hurts so much.
Guess doing things as you pleased
didn't really work out for you.
Here's my way what he's gone I've
lost contact with him there's no way I!
Refuse to believe it damn that rookie!
He did it.
It's around here somewhere.
Someone had the goals to take my car!
Where's the car?
Is this going to kill me?
Huh, that's Malone's bike.
There's only one way to catch these guys.
Leave no stone unturned and
think outside the box, they said.
I get leaving no stone unturned.
Any idiot would.
I mean, who hasn't turned
over rocks to find stuff?
But what the hell is thinking outside
the box even supposed to mean?
Maybe I think better in there damn it.
So my brains in a box now That's
the dumbest thing I've ever heard.
You think I'm an idiot capsule
Hey Malone Bucciarati and
his crew are in the wind
Are you listening? Hello?
Yes, I hear you don't go
counting me out just yet.
I Still possess Bucciarati's lifeblood
mass-producing juniors will be simple
They'll hunt him down in no time.
Hope you're right about that, Malone.
This new guy is a problem.
We have to dispose of him first.
I'll find us a truly
wicked surrogate who will
give birth to a powerful
and vicious beast.
A beast that will be starving for blood.
Huh? What the hell? A snake?
Am I losing it? What? What's wrong?
Why's a snake in Reimi Termini?
What? It's burning!
This must be that annoying newbie's doing.
He must have used Junior's corpse to...
Pronto?
Melode, what's going on over there?
Hey, answer me!
The venomous snake I left at the
terminal just went back to being junk.
And with this user's
defeat, five are dead.
If our info is correct, only two
members of the Hitman team remain.
Still, there's no time to rest.
Let's hightail to Venice!
They got Malone too?
It's me.
I've analyzed you-know-what.
I'm sending my findings over now.
We have a new directive from the boss.
Abokyo, I'd like you to
take a look at something.
All right.
This is the message.
A bakyo is to activate Moody Jazz by the
chair and rewind time
by more than 14 hours.
That means that someone must have been
residing here before we came along.
At least that's what this is implying.
If that's so, then let's see
where 15 hours back takes us.
A form is appearing.
Hey guys, haven't we
seen this old guy before?
Signore Pericolo.
So it must have been he who placed the
turtle by the fountain at Napoli Cinderella.
And about 14 hours ago, he was
standing where we are right now.
Resuming playback.
Listen to me carefully, Ragazzi.
I'm relaying the specifics
of your final mission. Hmm?
Final mission?
Strict confidentiality requires me to
adopt this bizarre mode of communication.
Under no circumstances are you
to share any of the following,
as you will now learn the way that
Trish has to be delivered to the boss.
A special way?
For us to deliver Trish, huh?
Now let's get to it.
When you arrive in Venice, you
are to proceed to this sculpture.
Inside, you will find
and obtain the OA disc.
It contains specifics concerning
the location of the handover.
What the hell is he doing?
Abbacchio, pause the playback. Right.
Of course, the gateway to the City
of Water, Santa Lucia Station.
See the lion statue?
And that's it.
Your job is to obtain the OA disk.
By now, the enemy is
aware of my influence.
So the way in which you deliver,
Trish, is absolutely critical.
Discretion's our most powerful ally.
Not a shred of evidence
can be left behind.
I've lived a full life thanks to
the boss's innumerable blessings.
It was replete with adventures
most can only dream of.
My mission is now complete.
Be safe, Ragazzi, and may
my prayers reach his ears.
Oh my god!
Mr. Pericolo...
Surely they've received
the directive by now.
You must obtain the disc, lest our
meeting be met with extreme difficulty.
Our fate rides on that final moment.
Bring Trish here.
Bring my daughter to me.
To Venice.
Floating in the ethereal dawn
lies the fortress city, Venice.
Only one road connects the Italian
mainland with the island's center,
the Ponte della Libertà, which stretches
three kilometers over a shallow lagoon.
Beyond it sits the station.
The Venetian Lion, which houses the
mysterious disk, can be found there.
Giorno, looks like we're in the
clear, at least for the moment.
Got it.
Same thing up front.
The city is still asleep.
We're the only ones on the road. Huh?
Why do these windows keep fogging up?
Are you trying to kill me? I'm sorry.
I guess the tires are
skidding a little bit.
On a road as straight as this one?
Jeez, who taught you to drive?
Wait, do you even have a license?
I'm 15, so no.
Huh? The hell?
There's something stuck to the window.
And it's on the inside.
I was so focused on looking
out, I didn't notice.
Hey, wait!
That thing looks like a...
a finger!
Then let's crack the windows a bit.
The condensation is being caused
by the difference in temperature.
What in the world?
What is with this wind?
The thought of losing that
chilled me to the bone.
Luckily, once we did some
computer analysis on the ashes,
Piecing together the photo Pericolo
burned was surprisingly easy.
What an idiotic move!
Did you fools really think you had
what it took to escape the hit?
Damn it! Another one!
How did they get up there?
Mista, what are you doing?
Start firing through the roof!
This damn car, it's like it's
being cryogenically frozen.
It's so cold my whole body's numb.
My little finger got ripped clean off,
and I didn't notice it sticking
to the window like a frozen fish.
And if I can't peel myself off,
my brain will get frozen over.
But do I really want to
live life with half a face?
Where's the turtle?
I'm not seeing a reptile anywhere.
The two of you aren't traveling
with Trish and Bucciarati?
Must be pretty important
to risk separating.
I got it.
You've been given a special
assignment to retrieve something big.
The place in the picture.
Something's at Santa Lucia.
Finally, I'm actually bleeding!
It's ice!
He covered himself in ice and
stuck himself to the roof!
The bullets are freezing
before getting to the bastard!
What's wrong?
Oh no, you guys!
All of us are starting to freeze too!
Somebody save me!
Number two, no!
Don't go!
Number two!
Number three!
What the?
Shit!
I just blinked!
Now my eyelashes are
stuck! Damn it to hell!
The guy was just lying in wait
for a chance to jump on the roof.
We're traveling 80 kilometers
an hour right about now.
Meaning that the wind is blowing around us
at approximately 20 kilometers a second.
and the wind chill factor drops one degree
Celsius for every meter of wind speed.
In layman's terms, we're all freezing
to death at minus 20 degrees Celsius.
Then stop the car!
Or were you planning on hitting the
brakes after we freeze to death?
Well, it's funny you
should mention the brakes.
The stupid pedal is frozen
solid and won't fudge an inch.
The steering wheel's useless,
but the engine's humming,
so at least we're good there.
The car's exterior has dropped to
minus 100 degrees it's happening
so fast this has got to be the
enemy's stand the blood from
my separate finger is frozen it's
as hard as a rock hey journal
the moisture from my breath is
making my damn nostrils freeze?
Oh, it's my lips. Oh,
shit. I can't breathe.
Stop the car!
Giorno, turn the damn thing into
a freaking frog if you gotta.
I don't care what you do.
Just do it fast.
Sorry, I already tried that before.
Problem is, nothing can survive
at minus 100 degrees Celsius.
Everyone knows the capital of France,
but English speakers pronounce it Paris,
while most say Paris the
way it's supposed to be.
But somehow Venice has replaced the
real Venice as the global standard.
Like those stories, The Merchant
of Venice and Death in Venice.
Why?
Call the damn book Death in Venice!
It's not that hard!
Are we not good enough?
Learn a little Italian, puttana, and
call the thing what it's supposed to be!
What kind of puppet
bullshit are they on about?
So the cold is finally starting
to affect your driving.
Sorry about golden wind, Mista,
but I can't use it without warmth.
I'm really sorry about all this, but
there's not much I can do at this point.
Besides picking up bullets.
It seems you've about reached your limit
as far as blowing holes in the car.
Now I'll put your body
into an even deeper freeze.
Huh?
Bullets retain a little heat
after being fired, right?
So, if I fire the ones Giorno picked
up, then I'm packing literal heat.
Speaking of him, he's at a loss for words,
so I'll do him a solid just this once.
Get rid of this freak, golden wind!
Success!
I know the sprouts don't look like much,
but those little plant
roots are strong enough to
tear up asphalt and demolish
boulders into pieces!
Hold on to the wheel, Torno!
We've gotta move!
Just as Malone said, the newbie
must have pulled this stunt.
But you don't get off that easy!
Give me a break. Already?
He's after us again!
I'll swoop in and make off with the goods
before those fools even know what's what.
You're wasting your bullets.
White Ice's specialty
is freezing the moisture
in the air at extremely low temperatures.
That's how I create my shimmering armor.
It's great for skating
on almost any surface.
And an added benefit is the way
it stops your pesky bullets!
It's...
Pastor Giorno!
It can't go any faster!
The tires are slipping all over the road!
What's worse, these guys know all
about what's waiting at the station!
That may be true,
but they still don't have the clues
to where Trish and the turtle are,
which, if you ask me, is a
pretty damn good silver lining.
There's that trademark optimism.
Yet again, you're a special one.
He's catching up!
Step on it!
Look, we can't, all right?
We'll just lose speed if we start
sliding around the road again!
I don't care!
Just do it, all right?
I told you, you're wasting your time!
Numbers two and three, get
over here on the double!
Hope you like asphalt.
Because you're about to get intimately
acquainted with the taste of it real quick.
Yahoo!
We lost Freaky the Snowman.
Now let's get out of here.
The station's just ahead.
We'll grab the disk as planned and
hide before he catches up to us.
We can do this, Giorno.
A nice plan, but keep dreaming.
He'll never make it to the station.
Not if I have my way.
It's freezing moisture
from the exhaust pipe.
Just how cold does it have to
be for that shit to freeze over?
Bastard, here's another dose of hot light.
He just popped open the trunk,
which means he's gonna...
This is bad!
We've got unwanted cargo!
Stop the car, Giorno!
That maniac is gonna try
freezing the brakes again!
You should stop wasting your
breath, you gun-bondling kagakatsu!
Seeing as how Trish is absent, I
can now do what I came here to do.
Shatter!
Giorno, your stairs!
It only cracked?
What's it going to take to kill him?
How do I dissolve his armor?
Giorno, could you stand
away from this guy?
I can't! Not just yet!
We've made it to Venice!
Hang on, we're going in now!
Every time I close my eyes,
I wake up feeling so horny.
I can't get you out of my mind,
since you'll be all I see.
I would give anything.
Just to make you understand me.
I don't give a damn about nothing else.
Freaking you is all I need.
I need your body.
You won't decide.
You got my mind.
I wanna do it for you.
What must I say?
What must I do?
To show how much.
I'm gonna feed you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Just myself.
But you must not get it.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Thank you.